<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Bigsister Blog Feed</title>
    <link>https://bigsister.live/blog</link>
    <description>RSS feed generated from https://bigsister.live/blog</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Do Parents Know What Their Children See Online?</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/do-parents-know-what-their-children-see-online</link>
      <description>Every child these days has a phone or access to the internet, but how much of that online activity are parents actually aware of? Let's explore the reality of parental awareness regarding their children's online experiences.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the Stars Messaging App?</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/what-is-the-stars-messaging-app</link>
      <description>Stars is a private messaging platform designed specifically for children and families. Explore its functions, purpose and capabilities in this blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The shocking rise of grooming in the uk</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/the-shocking-rise-of-grooming-in-the-uk</link>
      <description>Grooming cases have risen significantly in the UK since COVID, alarming parents and the government into action. This blog breaks down the stats and looks towards a brighter future</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ofcom's Landmark Guidelines for Online Safety</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/ofcoms-landmark-guidelines-for-online-safety</link>
      <description>The UK's Online Safety Act introduces groundbreaking protections against digital abuse, focusing on swift content removal and platform accountability to create a safer online space for women and girls.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In The Room: Intimate Image Abuse</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/legislative-change-on-intimate-image-abuse-at-parliament</link>
      <description>Intimate Image Abuse instances have risen dramatically for both children and adults across the UK. See what changes advocates brought to this parliamentary session to help protect victims.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Scrolling, Start Talking: A Parent's Guide to Online Safety</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/stop-scrolling-start-talking-a-parents-guide-to-online-safety</link>
      <description>Are you constantly checking your child's phone to ensure their online safety? Discover how to protect your kids in the digital age without breaking trust.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Big Sister Send Alerts?</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/how-does-big-sister-send-alerts</link>
      <description>See how Big Sister sends alerts and explore the app’s capabilities</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does Big Sister Identify threats?</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/how-does-big-sister-identify-threats</link>
      <description>Learn how Big Sister’s advanced AI-powered app identifies threats such as cyberbullying and grooming.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Safety for Children: A Parent's Guide to Smartphones</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/how-to-navigate-giving-your-child-a-smart-phone-at-christmas</link>
      <description>Ensure your child's online safety with our comprehensive guide on introducing smartphones and managing screen time. Empower your child to navigate the internet responsibly while enjoying their favorite online activities.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In The Room: Protection of Children Bill</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/in-the-room-protection-of-children-bill</link>
      <description>Big Sister attends a committee hearing for the Protection of Children Bill (Digital Safety and Data Protection). The bill aims to enhance online safety for children by increasing accountability for tech companies. Big Sister’s presence underscores our commitment to advocating for children's rights and safety in the digital landscape.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Report Harmful Digital Content</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/how-to-report-harmful-content</link>
      <description>How to report harmful content? Learn how to report harmful content seen on your child’s phone to the right authorities and find useful links for further support.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Big Sister Different?</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/what-makes-big-sister-different</link>
      <description>Explore what makes Big Sister different to other online safety apps for children and teenagers. See how Big Sister sets itself apart with AI-powered detection and expert-curated safety features, protecting children from online threats.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Safety: Government Priorities</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/online-safety-government-priorities</link>
      <description>NEWS: The UK government is taking significant action to enhance online safety for children and teenagers through the Online Safety Act, which tasks Ofcom with implementing key priorities.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to keep my child safe online</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/how-to-keep-my-child-safe-online</link>
      <description>Discover essential strategies for keeping your child safe online in our comprehensive blog, &quot;How to Keep My Child Safe Online.&quot; Learn about fostering open communication, setting device limits, and utilizing tools like Big Sister for effective monitoring.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Online Safety Quiz</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/the-online-safety-quiz</link>
      <description>Big Sister’s online safety quiz helps children and adults understand digital safety and potential next steps for difficult issues.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need: Online safety</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/everything-you-need-online-safety</link>
      <description>Online safety is evolving and it’s important to be aware of the tools and support systems out there available to both parents and children. Here’s everything you need to know about online safety.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While you wait for Big Sister</title>
      <link>https://bigsister.live/blog/blog/while-you-wait-for-big-sister</link>
      <description>Big Sister is coming soon, while you wait here’s how you can protect your child online.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
